<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
  <title>GSD Mobile</title>
  <link>https://github.com/rgocal/GSD-Mobile-2/MonthlyFeed.rss</link>
  <description>A RSS dedicated to monthly blog at GSD.</description>


 <item>
    <title>Scheduled Uodates</title>
    <description>Sapphyx Launcher Service Pack is expected to receive an update this week prior to the public launch of Sapphyx Launcher 2.0. It will have no affect on previous users and preps for major changes in Sapphyx Launcher 2. Also is expected are updates for Drywall and GSD Mobile for general maintenance. </description>
    <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p><img class="alignnone size-large wp-image-826374" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Mo3Mc5Z7cDK8frcmv_jB-D4Q5_fBLoHCucSaPxMIvfxD7dJqgxaI7SXP8VcK1RfDlQ=w300-rw">
]]>
</content:encoded>
  <link></link>
    <pubDate>6/18/2018</pubDate>
  </item>


<item>
    <title>Sapphyx 2 Public Beta</title>
    <description>The Sapphyx Launcher 2.0 public beta will be going live this weekend. In preparations, I will be keeping low on anything I've implemented in my latest private builds so it's something you can experience on your own. Sapphyx will have a hangouts and telegram group you may access at anytime for questions, feedback, request and general comments or even a good ol handshake. Users who currently have Sapphyx Launcher V1 installed from Google Play will receive this update as a regular update as the same goes for whom who has downloaded it off XDA Labs. Sapphyx Launcher V1 will remain on xda labs for archive purposes. A Vidoc will release this week talking about the latest changes, development and future of Sapphyx 2. Only you can make this a successful project, im just the guy behind the screen. Il see you at phase 2.</description>
    <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p><img class="alignnone size-large wp-image-826374" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Mo3Mc5Z7cDK8frcmv_jB-D4Q5_fBLoHCucSaPxMIvfxD7dJqgxaI7SXP8VcK1RfDlQ=w300-rw">
]]>
</content:encoded>
  <link></link>
    <pubDate>6/24/2018</pubDate>
  </item>

 <item>
    <title>Phase 2 ViDoc</title>
    <description>I will be presenting the community a Vidoc very soon displaying the current progress of Sapphyx Launcher 2.0 and its current features and talking about the public Beta. Stay tuned!.</description>
    <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p><img class="alignnone size-large wp-image-826374" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Mo3Mc5Z7cDK8frcmv_jB-D4Q5_fBLoHCucSaPxMIvfxD7dJqgxaI7SXP8VcK1RfDlQ=w300-rw">
]]>
</content:encoded>
  <link></link>
    <pubDate>6/18/2018</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>June Blog Live</title>
    <description>This month, its about phase 2 development of Sapphyx Launcher and were we currently stand with the project.</description>
    <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p><img class="alignnone size-large wp-image-826374" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Mo3Mc5Z7cDK8frcmv_jB-D4Q5_fBLoHCucSaPxMIvfxD7dJqgxaI7SXP8VcK1RfDlQ=w300-rw">
]]>
</content:encoded>
  <link>https://gocalsd.weebly.com/newsletter/sapphyx-phase-2</link>
    <pubDate>6/3/2018</pubDate>
  </item>
    <item>
    <title>Deprecation Notice!</title>
    <description>Sapphire Launcher has be suspended off of the Google Play store due to a security bug by Google Services. An end of the summer patch is expected to drop to fix it up and general maintenance.</description>
      <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p><img class="alignnone size-large wp-image-826374" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Mo3Mc5Z7cDK8frcmv_jB-D4Q5_fBLoHCucSaPxMIvfxD7dJqgxaI7SXP8VcK1RfDlQ=w300-rw">
]]>
</content:encoded>
  <link></link>
          <pubDate>6/9/2018</pubDate>
  </item>
    <item>
    <title>Sapphyx Launcher Suspension</title>
    <description>Sapphyx Launcher V1 has been suspended off of Google Play due to the numerous amounts of bugs and Google Play Services security issues floating around. Users can still view the application and recieve the 2.0 update when it becomes available. New customers cannot download or find it on the play store.</description>
      <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p><img class="alignnone size-large wp-image-826374" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/J98KBaEt-tF-3HtWvSkCPwERUfluVWxRIXMa_Z_zte0NnMSNAUr0MBV-_tI2ZD7RuAU=w170">
]]>
</content:encoded>
  <link></link>
          <pubDate>6/9/2018</pubDate>
  </item>
    <item>
    <title>Sapphyx Launcher 2.0 Private Alpha</title>
    <description>The private Alpha has begun! Email me for any interest or information regarding testing! A Telegram Gooup and Hangouts Group has been created for discussion. The Telegram group will remain open after release for discussions, help, and request.</description>
      <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p><img class="alignnone size-large wp-image-826374" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/J98KBaEt-tF-3HtWvSkCPwERUfluVWxRIXMa_Z_zte0NnMSNAUr0MBV-_tI2ZD7RuAU=w170">
]]>
</content:encoded>
  <link></link>
          <pubDate>3/24/2018</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Sapphyx Service Pack 2</title>
    <description>An update is scheduled to release for Sapphyx Service Pack very soon. It will not affect users on Sapphyx V1 as the new features, settings, and patches will not affect you. The update will be focused for V2 Alpha testers.</description>
      <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p><img class="alignnone size-large wp-image-826374" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/J98KBaEt-tF-3HtWvSkCPwERUfluVWxRIXMa_Z_zte0NnMSNAUr0MBV-_tI2ZD7RuAU=w170">
]]>
</content:encoded>
  <link></link>
          <pubDate>3/24/2018</pubDate>
  </item>
</channel>

</rss>
